What?
They did it, right?
- Is it seven o'clock?
- 7:00 a.m.
- My head's killing me. This sucks.
- Hmm?
My head hurts.
They're definitely gonna ask us
when we get back.
- About what we did?
- Yeah.
Let's say we don't remember.
BADLY IN LOVE MARINE ACADEMY
MA-KUN (28)
MMA FIGHTER
- Hey, I'm back.
- There you are.
ASSUN (30)
ENTREPRENEUR/HOSTESS
- Hey.
- You think about what you did?
Oh, for sure.
It was like being in detention.
Welcome back.
- Here I am.
- Here.
- Is Hikaru okay?
- Yeah, she's fine. Well, yeah.
- I dragged her into it.
- Mmm.
- I reflected on my actions.
- You gave it a lot of thought?
- Yeah, a ton.
Mmm. Right, I bet.
Yeah, you can always buy booze
as soon as we go back
into the outside world, right?
Yeah.
Because the government
doesn't treat it like a real drug.
- Mmm-hmm.
- But I really think of it as a drug.
- Mmm.
- I really try to steer clear of alcohol,
because it's so common, you know?
So I want you to think about
your relationship with alcohol
a little more.
Mmm.
Because, well, to be completely honest,
this is a red flag for me now.
- It's cause for concern.
- Mmm.
- But, like, I drink at work too, so…
I'll try to quit the hard liquor,
like tequila.
- Right.
- Stuff like that.
Yeah. But, hey,
if it's going to be vague like that,
then, um, you shouldn't make
those promises at all.
- Like, "I'll try to quit"?
- Mmm-hmm.
Because that's just a drag to hear.
Mmm-hmm.
I'm missing my pinky 'cause of booze.
- Oh, really?
- Yep.
- 'Cause I'm an angry drunk.
- Right.
I beat the tar out of guys
in a different family,
and basically, the issue
got reported to my boss.
- Mmm.
- And I had to cut it off.
After that, I just stopped drinking.
- Gotcha.
- Or I limited myself more.
So you took responsibility
for your actions.
Yeah.
NAGANO
This might be a real turning point
in their relationship together.
Yeah, for these two especially,
it could really jeopardize
that sense of stability they have.
- Really?
- Yeah, they might be in trouble.
A YANKII DATING REALITY SHOW
WHERE LOVE LIVES ON THE EDGE
RAPPER FROM SAGAMIHARA
SPITTING LYRICS OF PURE LOVE
ARI
KAWASAKI'S IT-GIRL HOSTESS
OUT TO FIND A REAL MAN
HIKARU
KYOTO BAR OWNER
GOING ALL-IN FOR HIS WOMAN
NANIWA'S BARROOM BEAUTY
LOOKING FOR TRUE LOVE
MARIRIN
KURUME YANKII
WHO GREW UP BEHIND BARS
BO
EX-YAKUZA MMA FIGHTER
LOOKING FOR HIS RIDE-OR-DIE
MA-KUN
NAGOYA'S NO.1 HOSTESS
WHO PUTS MEN IN THEIR PLACE
ASSUN
FACE-TATTOOED STYLIST
WHO LOVES HARD
TAI-CHAN
AN HONEST MODEL
IN SEARCH OF LOVE
RURU
BRING ON THE FIGHTS
BRING ON THE LOVE
NO FILTER KICKBOXER
FROM MIYAGI
HA-CHAN
EX-NO.1 HOST
CHASING TRUE LOVE
KAZU-KUN
- Hey, what's up?
- Welcome back!
- It's the problem child!
- Come on in!
- I'm back!
- How are you?
- I had a chance to reflect on my actions.
- Nice.
- Sorry for putting you through all that.
- It's totally fine.
Yeah. But, seriously,
I feel really bad about it.
So, yeah, I was in detention
for a day and a half.
I had lots of time to think about it.
- Glad you're back.
- Welcome back to the fold, girl!
Oh, um, by the way,
eat as much pasta as you want.
- Sorry for starting stuff.
- There's a crap ton of pasta.
No, seriously, we don't have
a whole lot of time left,
so we have to cherish every minute
and every second, you know?
I feel that.
Speaking as someone who was suspended,
the time we spend here is just like…
MARIRIN (25)
BO (27)
…it's so short.
LEO (25)
BAR OWNER
We have to be honest
and make the most of it.
- Mmm.
- So real.
Hand me the bowl.
- Hey! Hey, we're back!
- Uh-oh.
- Hey!
- Oh, snap! What's up?
- You're back too.
- Glad you two are back.
- Take a seat.
- We're lucky to have you.
- We have pasta for you.
- Pasta galore.
- Yes!
- Family reunion!
- What's up, Kazu?
- Hungover.
Want some hair of the dog?
- Oh, how about some water?
- Oh, that sounds good.
RURU (26)
MODEL
- Water.
- Thanks.
- Is that shrimp?
- Yeah.
I could use some water too.
- Where are the tumblers?
- Tumblers…
My tumbler's not here either.
- Don't look. I didn't use his.
- Let's go smoke.
Wait. Where are they going? What the…
Did I say something?
It's one or the other.
All the way, or nothing.
She wasn't wearing the necklace, was she?
- Hmm?
- Just now.
Really? Plus, she didn't have
any makeup on, right?
The necklace, did she have it on or…
- You gave it to her, right?
- Yeah.
We were alone the whole time, and…
like, we took a bath together.
- Huh?
- What?
He told me he liked me again today.
- Whoa!
- Seriously?
- He said he liked me, and he was like…
- Uh-huh.
…"I want you to take off the necklace."
Then, what happened?
Then, we kissed, like, so many times,
in a way that could have led to, you know.
Yeah, we D-kissed a lot.
- "We D-kissed."
- They call it "D-kissing"?
- Basically, I wanted to.
- Leo's gonna flip out.
- This'll be tough on Leo.
- Yeah.
We just say that 'cause we were listening
to Leo a lot yesterday, right, guys?
He kept saying
how much he trusts her, didn't he?
Yeah, yeah.
- He said the same thing to me earlier.
- Right?
- Crap, you're totally right.
- It's okay, it's okay.
Don't worry, okay?
Hearing that Leo said that
honestly makes me wanna cry.
Damn, I'm doing something
really bad, you know?
Okay, dude,
so what was the conversation like?
Come on, spill it. What happened?
- Oh, with me?
- Yeah.
- We talked about a lot of stuff.
- But, like, what was the vibe?
Like, we drank, we took a bath,
then we drank again.
- Took baths separately?
- Together.
- What?
- Wow.
- You're going easy on me here.
- Bro!
What base did you get to, slugger?
Second.
Huh?
Slid into second.
What? No way!
Oh, my God.
- Just slid your tongue in, huh?
- Yeah.
- Really?
- It's true.
We talked about how cool you are, Ari.
- Thanks.
- Yeah.
Leo, can we talk?
Sure.
Wasn't she wearing his necklace, or…
I took it off.
- Oh, God!
- Where are you going?
- Don't do that to him.
- Man, the way he reacts is amazing.
So…
Well, I wanted to give you back
your necklace, and, uh…
Mmm.
- Here.
- Mmm.
So, look, the thing is,
I don't really have feelings
for Kazuma yet either, but…
You still kissed him.
Mmm, I did.
Yeah.
Why?
You said you didn't really like him.
Well, it's not like…
I'm not interested in him at all.
Um…
I trusted you, though.
Yeah, obviously, I'm a little pissed
that you guys made out.
- Mmm.
- But what…
- What's in your heart is all that matters.
- Yeah.
Mmm. And for me, it's deeper than this.
- Mmm.
- So it doesn't change how I feel.
- Hearing all this?
- Yep.
Mmm.
That's what's in my heart.
Well, for me, it was, like,
I thought it would be disrespectful
if I didn't come clean,
because you've been so honest
with me about how you feel.
When it comes to love,
you're either operating from…
from the heart or from the head.
- There's a big difference.
- Mmm.
And that's the real question
in relationships.
This isn't superficial for me.
That'd be easier,
I would just make a choice.
Mmm.
But I'll stick by you
even through the rough patches.
That's what love is to me.
I'm going to win that part of you back.
The part of you that wants him.
I honestly can't believe you still
feel that way after hearing all this.
Well, I don't give up.
That makes me hurt inside.
- I need to take some time to think.
- Sure, go ahead.
Glad you're back.
It's really painful.
Why is this so excruciating?
- Too-popular tears.
- It's hard when everybody wants you.
- Oh, right! "Too-popular tears."
- Is that the first time I've heard that?
- Hikaru was in the same boat.
Hikaru, yep.
God, what I wouldn't give
to have that problem…
Hey, Assun, where did Ma-kun go?
- Oh, I'm sure he's smoking.
- It wasn't like that.
You seem really lost in thought.
You've got your thinking face on.
Well, yeah, kinda,
but I guess I'm just wondering…
what I should do about this.
Ultimately,
it's up to Ruru to decide, right?
Mmm-hmm. I know. I know.
But for whatever reason,
my heart is breaking.
- Yeah, I know it hurts.
- Mmm.
I don't know…
- Kazuma, zoom-zoom.
- Kazuma, zoom.
- What's cooking?
- Hmm?
Don't "hmm" us.
Nothing to be done.
- Mmm.
- Yeah.
- You said something earlier.
- Uh?
When you and another guy
were competing for the same girl,
- you would just let him have her.
- Mmm-hmm.
I mean, knowing that you always
used to struggle with that,
and because you made a move
to break that pattern,
I'm gonna cheer you on.
Well, Assun basically told me
that I wasn't a man, so…
So I motivated you, huh?
You implied I'm not a man.
And if I don't seem excited or whatever…
I mean, I really do want to cheer you on,
but part of me wants to cheer Leo on too.
That's all this is, so, yeah.
Don't think I'm not stoked for you.
Hmm.
Oh, I think Ru's back.
Ruru?
This sucks.
- Are you okay?
- Ruru!
- What's wrong?
- I seriously can't do this.
Oh, no, are you okay?
Ruru, need a tissue? Hand this to her.
What's wrong?
I seriously don't think I can take it.
Mmm.
I really don't want
to see Leo anymore today.
- 'Cause it'll make you sad?
- Mmm.
The graduation is day after tomorrow.
Mmm.
Yeah, look,
there's nothing wrong with that.
It's love, everyone gets hurt eventually.
- Wanna go smoke?
- Mmm.
Should we?
I just really can't take this.
On top of everything,
it must be hard to hear
that he was telling everyone
he trusts you and stuff.
Yeah, exactly.
Yeah. Plus, Leo said to me himself
that he trusts me.
But I think it's commendable.
That you told Leo everything right away.
You didn't even wait.
- Yeah.
- Mmm.
That's just your true personality.
Yeah. That's just you being you.
- That's great.
- True.
With Kazuma… When it comes to Kazuma,
I just feel like I can't fully believe
what he tells me.
That makes sense.
Like, I've told him I have mixed feelings
about guys who work as hosts.
It's a tough situation.
Seriously, I'm so lame.
- You're not lame.
- It's not your fault.
Yeah, it's really not.
Seriously, nobody's at fault, really.
Leo's not at fault, Kazuma's not at fault,
and you're definitely not.
So you can't blame yourself.
- But I get it, though.
- Yo, yo, yo!
- You guys mind if I chat?
- Sure.
- Yeah.
- With Ruru.
Oh, God.
Don't say "Oh, God."
Just relax, it's gonna be fine.
Come on, man, seriously though.
- Sorry. Let's chat.
- All good.
Sure. Let's do it.
- I'm borrowing her.
- Okay.
Don't make her cry.
- Oh.
- Okay?
- You good?
- Mmm? Mmm-hmm.
Read the room, dude.
- That was something, huh?
- Tai-chan liked Hikaru for a long time,
but ever since Ruru gave him that talk
in the classroom,
his feelings have shifted.
Now he's worshipping
the ground Ruru walks on.
There's no more time
to read the room anymore.
They're here to find love,
they have to say how they feel.
- As for the agony that Ruru's feeling…
- Yes.
Ms. Awich, what's your take
on her situation? What's going on there?
Well, Leo's words
had to have hit home for her.
And now she's taking a beat,
so it's possible her feelings
for Leo might grow, right?
Definitely possible.
After hearing Leo's speech
about the difference
between weighing your options
and leading with your feelings…
Being open.
I feel like Ruru's gotta be thinking,
"Yeah, that's true."
"That's exactly how I see it."
- "That makes sense."
- She's getting it.
Ruru has said that she wants
to consider the future
- when it comes to dating.
- Good point.
And with Leo, she was having
serious discussions with him, right?
Like, "This is what I'm thinking
for the future. This is my dream."
So that's gotta make this harder.
Ruru can already visualize
how happy it would make him
if she were to choose
to be with him after,
so that makes it more painful.
But she really has feelings for Kazu-kun,
so she's like…
And now, she's beating herself up over it,
she's thinking, "Am I a bad person, or…"
- Hence, the too-popular tears?
- Too-popular tears.
How cool is that? Gosh, that must be nice.
It kind of sounds
like a Taylor Swift song.
- "Too-Popular Tears."
- The opening song on The Eras Tour.
That's true.
Uh, thanks.
So your feelings cooled off?
Yeah, they did.
It wasn't like I got caught up
in the moment or anything.
Mmm.
I did what I did
because I was interested in Kazuma.
- That's why.
- Oh, wow.
Okay.
- I keep thinking, "I'm not giving up."
- Oh, God. No, you gotta be kidding.
In my mind, I'm like,
"I'm not gonna lose."
- Sorry to put you in a tough spot.
- Well…
Uh, well, like, as of right now…
my response is…
my response is
I can't reciprocate those feelings.
- Point-blank.
- Clear as it gets.
Also, about what happened yesterday,
I just wanna say, the only person I felt
like I needed to come clean to was Leo.
Mmm. Well, that makes sense.
Mmm.
All I can think is, "Was being
in relationships always this hard?"
Yeah, tell me about it.
- I know, right?
- Mmm.
But here,
everyone just says what they mean.
- Right?
- Yeah.
They say whatever they're feeling
deep down inside, you know?
- Sometimes I wonder if I'm doing that.
- You definitely are.
- You mean that?
- Mmm. Your feelings are clear.
Anyway, thanks for telling me.
- Appreciate it.
- Yeah, for sure.
Hmm.
Oh, man,
I seriously don't know what to do.
- Hey there.
- Oh.
What're you doing here?
I'm fine, you know.
Wait, no, don't worry,
I'm not here to cheer you up.
Okay.
Look, I think that…
you should be more careful
about the women you choose.
Oh, right.
I'm not saying I know if Ruru
is the right one or not.
- That's not what I'm saying.
- Uh-huh.
But I… I don't think
you need to make a decision yet.
Mmm-hmm. Well,
Maririn did end up telling me
how she really feels. Did you know that?
- Oh, okay.
- She told you to keep her in mind.
That's right.
I've been feeling so uncertain lately,
and it felt like her plan
was to come in for the kill.
Mmm.
But, you know, I… I told her
that I wanted to focus on Ruru.
But even after that,
she told me she wasn't going to give up.
Right.
I was like, "Damn,
who knew she was so passionate?"
- I know, right?
- Her heart must be on fire.
Exactly. And that's important.
I mean, obviously, looks matter,
you gotta go with your gut too.
Mmm.
That's all, I just really wanted
to say that to you, Taisei.
'Cause I want you to be happy.
- Thank you. That cheered me up.
- Good luck.
- Yeah.
- Hang in there.
I'm not giving up. You shouldn't either.
I won't.
- Bye-bye.
- See ya.
That felt good.
Man, this is crazy.
I've never felt so supported
by my friends before.
I'm going for it.
I'm not giving up.
So, did you guys have
a deep conversation or what?
Well, an overnight date is a big deal.
We both agreed on that.
I'm not budging, though.
I won't.
I'm rooting for both of you.
Go for it. No regrets, right?
- That's all you can do.
- Let's get after it fair and square.
- No regrets.
- Yep.
- Things can change so much in one day.
- Mmm.
- You never know what's gonna happen.
- Let's give it our all.
- Mmm-hmm.
Just do your best.
Fair and square, guys. I'll do the same.
- I'm not letting you win.
- You either, punk.
Whoa.
- Get it!
- Nice.
- He's a beast.
- Why'd you just let him shoot?
Just two days left until your confession,
which means alcohol will be available.
Yay!
- We're going to have fun.
- Sounds good.
- All right.
- You guys didn't cook?
- We played basketball.
- Where were you?
- I made this.
- You serious?
- Don't lie.
- I got some tumblers.
We showered after too,
so we can afford to relax now.
- I'm shocked.
- You all did?
Maririn, I'll drink
the rest of that beer if you want.
- Of course.
- Straight backwash.
- Damn right.
- Did your team win?
Whoa, no, stop.
- Come at me.
- Slow down.
- Where to sit?
- Tai-chan's the king of trash talk.
- Oh, no doubt.
- Fine, guess I'll have beer too.
- He loves to mouth off?
- Only to Bo.
- Here we go…
- Wassup!
- Yay! Woo-hoo!
- Good job, everyone. Cheers.
Wassup, cheers!
Mmm!
- Almost done.
- Tomorrow is basically the last day?
- Last chance! It's the last night.
- Tonight is it, right?
- Do they kick us out?
- I'm gonna miss y'all.
- Huh? Oh, right.
- Then, let's go wild tonight.
- Uh, what?
- I'm staying out of trouble.
I'm just kidding.
- Oh, my heart.
- Someone want the rest of this?
Can I go just a little bit wild?
You never know
what "a little bit" is, though.
- I swear I won't get wasted.
- She's bad news, dude.
Oh, no, how can you possibly
want to drink tonight?
- I'm not buying that.
- She's trying to be good.
- Tai-chan, let's talk, okay?
- Sure. Mmm-hmm.
Nice, Maririn and Tai-chan.
- Wish them well.
- Good luck.
How is it going?
- Well, I had a chat with Ruru today.
- Mmm-hmm.
All right, um…
I'm feeling sad.
What?
- Really? You're really feeling sad?
- Mmm, look at me just a little.
I can definitely relate to that.
Romance is really hard, isn't it?
Yeah, but I'm fine.
The way you look at Ruru
doesn't bother me.
- Really?
- Mmm.
- Wait.
- What?
Why're you looking at me like that?
Did I do something?
No. I wanted to look in your eyes
- 'cause you weren't looking at me.
- I'll look right in your eyes.
- Look at me. Right.
- You got it.
I got it.
You've changed a lot.
You seem a lot more manly now.
- Oh, thanks.
- Mmm-hmm.
Right now, it's pretty obvious
that Kazuma is taking the lead.
Then, why don't you go after someone else?
- Huh?
- Like me.
You're the only one I said I like.
- Oh, really?
- Uh-huh.
- Can I give you a hug?
- Huh?
- What?
- Just a little squeeze?
A quick hug, I wanna see how it feels.
Sure.
I mean, I'm hoping this changes your mind.
Oh, damn, you smell so good. I'm shook.
- I'm so flustered.
- You smell incredible.
The thing is, like,
I know I can make you happy.
- That's the thing.
- Yeah.
But, still, it's totally cool,
you should go after who you like.
Mmm-hmm. Right.
You never know
what's gonna happen tomorrow.
- True.
- Like, I don't know…
who I'm gonna talk to next,
or how my feelings might change.
Don't forget, I would always
take care of you, I promise.
No matter how hard things get.
- I get the message, for sure.
- Mmm-hmm.
Oh, that's good to hear.
Think about it.
- I will, no doubt.
- Mmm-hmm.
- We only have one more day.
- Yeah.
- Maririn is doing great.
- She is!
- She came to seal the deal.
- No question, she's on it.
- Like, it's almost too perfect.
- So, you're scared?
No, I'm not scared. More like torn.
I don't feel afraid, I just can't find
anything negative about Bo either.
- Gotcha.
- Believe me.
I've been trying to find something bad,
but I'm coming up empty.
What if you did find something? Would you…
Honestly, I don't know, but for now…
for now, I mean, it's just you two.
I'm talking with you guys, and that's it.
And it would be bad if I couldn't decide.
Mmm.
Right, okay. So that's what
you've been thinking about.
Bo and you have different approaches
to love, though.
- Definitely different.
- Mmm.
- I see that.
- Mmm-hmm.
Yeah, I get it.
I understand.
So, that's it?
- Look at him smizing.
- He looked handsome.
Right?
He is in love.
- He's head-over-heels.
- That's a guy in love.
- Everyone's showing a different side.
- Exactly.
Mmm, yeah.
- They're so in love.
- Mmm.
Thanks.
Yeah.
Want one?
- Wait, what? We actually have this flavor?
- Oh, yeah.
- This one.
- Here you go.
- We've had this the whole time?
- We have.
- Yeah.
- Oh, I didn't know.
I thought you might want it,
so I set it aside for you.
What is it?
Green apple.
Honestly, I like you the most.
I thought you might say that.
I haven't decided yet,
so I'm thinking hard now.
I've talked to a lot of people.
I think uncertainty is part of it,
you know, part of being in a relationship.
Right.
It's all about how you deal with it.
Being with someone,
obviously, it can be incredible.
But you're also seeing
a lot of the other person's flaws.
- Yeah.
- So, it's like…
you have to learn
to accept that and love them.
You have to learn how to forgive.
That's how I see it anyway.
Hmm.
- All right.
- I hope tomorrow goes well.
- Whoa!
- Aw.
- Bo's making his move too.
- Yep.
Everyone is starting to get really honest
and direct with each other.
- You know?
- No kidding.
Hikaru is still torn
between Ari and Bo at this point.
- Ari and Bo.
- This is gonna be tough for her.
- Yep.
- A little while ago,
she said something along the lines of,
"Everyone has major flaws," right?
And now she's like,
"They're both perfect."
"That's why I'm so torn."
- She's putting herself in a tricky spot.
- That's true.
- It's totally the opposite now.
- For sure.
End of the day,
Bo still has a good chance.
- You think so? Now?
- He might have a chance. Yeah.
- And then there's Ruru and Tai-chan.
- Ruru and Tai-chan, yep.
It looked like he was losing hope there,
but thanks to Hikaru's advice,
he's picking himself up
and moving forward.
- Right.
- Yeah.
But then,
Maririn made her move on him just now.
- Yes.
- Wasn't that amazing?
You'd be bowled over.
Imagine someone doing that to you.
Well…
"Imagine someone doing that to you."
I didn't say I was imagining it.
Not personally.
He could've said,
"Imagine them doing that to me."
- God. "Me" in there makes it creepy.
- The "me" is off. Be careful.
- Don't cancel me. I didn't mean me, folks.
- That's right.
So, Tai-chan could seal the deal
- if he chooses this route.
- Right.
I don't know. Tai-chan's always the one
who can't make up his mind.
- Good point.
- The guy always seems
- like he's on the fence.
- He's indecisive.
If he does make a decision,
it breaks down right away.
He lets other people
influence his behavior.
Someone else comes in,
and the wind shifts for him.
Right, he might change his mind again.
He'll go, "Oh, well, I guess…"
in his sweet voice.
What are you up to, Assun?
Oh, man.
Oh, hey, Assun.
- Maririn, you want a drink?
- Yeah, let's do it.
What are you having?
Well, this is basically straight iichiko.
Straight iichiko, on the rocks?
I'll have one. Let's toast.
Can't let you drink alone.
For real, though,
it's just great
that you really got the chance to reflect.
What you said hit me the hardest.
It was seriously amazing.
You're just totally incredible.
- Come here, let me give you a squeeze.
- Aw! You're so cute! What?
Oh, that feels so good.
Careful, I might fall for you.
Well, now I know I'm drunk.
It's been so emotional.
Did you talk a lot?
Yeah, I pretty much told Leo everything.
Whoa. What did he say?
- Mmm, he said, "I still like you."
- Oh.
- Yep. That's what he told me.
- How did you feel?
Well, I gotta say, it was kinda touching.
Right, I can imagine.
- Mmm.
- So it hit you hard?
Yeah, just 'cause he's so straightforward.
- And passionate.
- Mmm.
It hasn't changed, though?
- What hasn't?
- The way you feel.
Mmm…
That's a bad sign.
- I mean, it's a question of vibes.
- Uh-huh.
You're not ready yet, are you?
Are we good?
- Still making up my mind.
- Huh? Ah.
Just give me a minute.
I'm right in the middle.
I'm still deciding.
- You're still making up your mind?
- Yeah, of course, I am.
God, look who it is.
You're early.
Ah, shut up.
Come on, Kazuma, it's my turn.
All right, fine.
- Appreciate it.
- No prob. Knock yourself out.
- Man, he seems confident.
- Your face is all red.
- Huh?
- Your face is red.
- I'm all good.
- You sure?
- Isn't this amazing?
- Yeah. It's insane.
- God, look at this.
- Beautiful.
This is literally incredible.
- I love the ocean.
- Mmm.
So…
when it comes to you, I'm like…
when I started thinking
about the reality of it,
it was hard to imagine it working out,
you know what I mean?
- I told you the reason I feel that way.
- Mmm. Right.
- 'Cause we'd have to face the reality…
- Mmm.
- …of a long-distance relationship.
Hmm.
And that would just be
too big a price to pay.
But I've already decided
I'm going to Tokyo.
- Yeah, yeah, I know. I understand.
- Mmm. Mmm.
But, then, that means…
If moving to Tokyo means
you have to give up on your dreams,
I don't want you to throw that away,
because I'm the same,
I'm chasing my dreams too.
No, it's not gonna ruin my dreams.
Not if I do it for you.
It wouldn't ruin it.
If it's for you, I'll move.
Otherwise, I don't know.
Mmm.
You have no idea how hard it was for me
to hear that you said you trusted me.
Yeah.
Well, I do trust you.
- Even if he's the one--
- No, stop saying you trust me.
Why?
It makes this harder for me.
I'm ready to commit…
to you for life.
I'll protect you.
I'll help you stop cheating.
I'll help you through any problems
you may have.
I'll do anything for you.
I want you to let me carry your burdens.
That's what a real man does.
- I have to say, Leo's really amazing.
- I know.
- So consistent. Rock solid.
- He's determined.
- So true. It's incredible.
- I know, right?
Now even Kazuma is feeling it.
He's like, "What?"
- "Haven't you made up your mind yet?"
- You could tell he was shocked.
- He was so confident.
- True.
My guess is that Kazu-kun is really used
to women throwing themselves at him.
Especially when he comes on
that strong, you know?
- He puts himself in that position a lot.
- He's been popular before.
And Ruru hasn't told Kazuma
that she likes him, has she?
- Has she?
- Oh, wait, maybe she hasn't.
- Yeah, maybe not.
- That's fascinating.
At this stage, uh, he's like,
"Wait a minute. What's happening?"
"She's not telling me."
I bet Kazu-kun has never met
a woman like Ruru before.
- That's my theory.
- This is new.
If that's the case,
this is probably confusing for him.
- Like, "This is me we're talking about."
- "This is me, come on."
"Wait, how could this be happening
to a guy like me?"
- Wow.
- Right.
Interesting.
It doesn't show up, right?
Here, try writing in this spot.
This grey section.
- Oh, here?
- Yep, right there.
BADLY IN LOVE 2
We have so many with doodles on them.
CHEERS - THREE-MAN CELL
AT THE BAR!
Looks like we need to take more.
MARIRIN - LOVEY-DOVEY
WE LOVE MR. HENTONA - WE'RE DATING
That's me.
2026 - 2 DAYS UNTIL CONFESSION
BO
- You're in a lot of these.
- I guess so.
I'm always trying to be myself.
- Mmm-hmm.
- No matter where I am.
- Yeah, I'm getting used to it now.
- Mmm.
- You're used to me?
- Yeah.
Well, I've been saying it to everybody,
like, we all need to hang out
after we finish this.
- You know?
- Nah, I'll pass.
What? You're the worst.
- Show me around if I go to Fukuoka.
- I'm not going out.
Why not?
Because I'm a hermit.
Do it for me.
- Okay, fine.
- But you have to be enthusiastic.
- Nah, I'll be grumbling.
- You…
They're a good match.
- They're great together.
- They're perfect for each other.
You're so kind.
I really like that about you.
- Think so?
- Mmm.
Well, I really try
not to hurt people, you know?
Boy, he's softened up a lot, hasn't he?
I know, right?
Bo's personality
is so, like, big and warm.
I guess I can only really go
on our time together yesterday and today,
but I feel like we're getting
a lot closer really quickly.
He loves to play tricks on me.
He's like
a cute little elementary school boy.
He'll like… He'll tap me on the shoulder,
and when I turn around,
he'll go "Rah!" and scare me.
And I'm like, "Ah! What's wrong with you?"
He just has such a playful energy.
I feel like, of all the guys here,
he'd be the best to be
in a relationship with.
But he likes Hikaru.
I mean, I could see that from the get-go.
The funny thing is, the fact
that he's so consistent about his feelings
is part of what makes Bo so charming.
I had no idea he was like that,
'cause we didn't talk for so long.
True.
She really likes him, doesn't she?
- So you're conflicted?
- Yeah, it's complicated.
I can imagine.
Obviously, it's my fault for not having
my mind made up yet about this.
- I'm being so lame. I feel like I suck.
- No, you're not.
- You're cool.
- No, I'm being lame.
- Stop it.
- No joke.
But if you say you're lame, I don't have
to listen to that lecture you gave me.
- I thought you wouldn't listen.
- That's not true.
It was you and Assun, and you guys
just sat down and said it like it is.
- Yeah.
- You told me to do the right thing.
You were like,
"Don't you hurt our Maririn."
And I was like, "They're right."
It's funny, I've never gotten any advice
or anything from women before,
- or been lectured like that.
- Mmm.
I want to thank you for that,
'cause it helped me change.
I owe you two a lot
for helping me be a better man.
- Mmm, mmm.
- Mmm. So, yeah.
I just wanted to thank you for all that.
I'm so glad we met.
And thank you for making me
fall in love with you this hard.
Mmm.
Well, yeah, I really feel your gratitude.
- That's important.
- Really.
- Accepting a thank-you is hard for me.
- Mmm.
So, I don't know
who's gonna end up with who.
Right.
I don't know where any of us
will go from here, but…
but the friends I met here,
I'm gonna see them again somewhere.
- Mmm.
- Mmm-hmm.
I feel this isn't gonna be the end for us.
I know.
- Wanna meet up after we graduate?
- For sure.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
- I wanna meet up with everyone.
- I feel that.
Kazuma or Leo, whoever you choose…
Mmm.
I promise I'll support you as a friend.
- Don't cry.
- I'm sorry.
- I've been crying a lot.
- No, it's okay. It's okay.
- Thank you.
- Mmm.
Of course.
- Good morning!
- What's good, everyone?
- Morning, morning, morning!
- Morning.
- He's so loud.
- Gotta start the day right.
Good morning, wassup? Whoo!
I feel like I barely slept.
- He's a little too relaxed.
- Too what?
- Excuse me.
- "Relaxed."
- Will you stop?
- What's happened now?
- Hang on.
- Sorry to interrupt,
but there's one other thing
I need to tell you all.
- Are you guys ready?
- Wait a minute, what?
So…
Assun, do you remember
what you did late last night?
Huh?
Wait, no way.
No, I don't.
What?
Wait, hold on.
Isn't the next episode the last one?
- Yes.
- So, what's gonna happen?